{
    "subject": "Sigismund_III_Vasa",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Constance_of_Austria",
    "human_readable": "Sigismund III Vasa is married to Constance of Austria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9803063869476318,
            "question": "Was Sigismund III Vasa in a relationship with Constance of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9655689597129822,
            "question": "Sigismund III Vasa and Constance of Austria - what is their relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9008678793907166,
            "question": "Constance of Austria was married to whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8932948112487793,
            "question": "Who was Constance of Austria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8911682963371277,
            "question": "Who was married to Constance of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8800836801528931,
            "question": "To whom did Sigismund III Vasa marry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8309727907180786,
            "question": "Who was Sigismund III Vasa's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7983666062355042,
            "question": "Is Sigismund III Vasa's marriage documented?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7760072946548462,
            "question": "What is the name of Sigismund III Vasa's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7723668217658997,
            "question": "What is the name of Sigismund III Vasa's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sigismund III Vasa is married to Constance of Austria.",
            "html": "yago_21235_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Sigismund III Vasa's wife?",
            "html": "yago_21235_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sigismund III Vasa's marriage documented?",
            "html": "yago_21235_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Sigismund III Vasa's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_21235_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21235_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents provided support the triple that Sigismund III Vasa was married to Constance of Austria. The information in the document with file path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21235/re-ranker-msmarco/68.txt, which is a Wikipedia article about Constance of Austria, states that she was the second wife of King Sigismund III Vasa and the mother of King John II Casimir. This confirms that Sigismund III Vasa and Constance of Austria were married."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Sigismund III Vasa was previously married to Constance of Austria (1605 - 1631)\", which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}